No living creature was harmed during
the filming of this series.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Osman Bey.
Stop.
I'm here on behalf of the Emperor.
You are fighting the wrong enemy.
I don't know with whom you work but...
we are not leaving here.
Allow me to explain to you.
Your son, Alaaddin...
is captured by Emperor's enemies.
What are you saying?
Enemies have entered our home.
How do you guard this door?
Are you blind?
Are you deaf?
Answer me, Alps!
- Who am I talking to?
- Bala Hatun.
Who am I talking to?
Answer me.
Bala Hatun.
Patience, Bala Hatun.
This is not the time to be angry.
Allah will surely help you.
We will find Alaaddin.
Aktemur
Is there a trace?
There are wheel traces.
However, there are
no traces ahead.
We have to trace it.
Let's go now.
Alps!
Get the horses ready!
Dursun Fakı.
Be careful.
Aladdin Ali, I will kill the ones
who uprooted you from your branch.
Who?
Who did this?
The ones who wanted to kill the emperor.
Ophelia.
Emperor's daughter.
But Ophelia is not alone.
Frigg, who is sent to this
country to destroy you...
These are our enemies, Osman Bey.
There is no such thing as "we".
You are on the side.
We are on the other side.
You had their enmity that day by
saving Constantinople.
If the enemy is one, then we
are one too, Osman Bey.
And that dog?
He is Olof, the most respected
warrior of Rome.
He wanted to avenge for
Öktem Bey's massacre in the village.
It's wrong.
Kantakuzenos.
If my son is hurt...
I will kill you all.
If I had been afraid of this, I wouldn't
have come with a few men.
I trust your friendship.
I believe we will destroy the game
those two demons created.
How did you know all these things?
I've been after them since that dark day.
I caught one of Frigg's men.
And it brought me to these places.
If you're lying...
I'll wrap that rope around
your neck with my hands.
Where is the man?
Underground.
Kantakuzenos.
Olof...
killed my Alps
and blamed them.
And you came to tell me about the
witness of a death.
How long do you allow
traitors to survive?
Or those who attacked the village?
Why did they kidnap my son?
They kidnapped him for Dan.
Dan is Frigg's brother.
Loyal maid of Ophelia.
Constantinople
Emperor's Palace
My beloved daughter, Ophelia.
She made a light and sturdy shield for me.
No harm will come
to you, Honorable Emperor.
That's why Kantakuzenos
asked me to stay by your side.
So, Kantakozanos loves me like Ophelia.
Are you okay, sir?
Yes.
There must have been a
needle left while making the shield.
How is that possible?
Princess Ophelia has acted with caution.
My Father
You tried the shield then
My father.
Father!
- Father!
- Stop it!
Stop, don't come close.
The shield may
be poisoned.
Hey, call the doctor quickly.
My Father.
Emperor!
Tell me everything.
This poison will slowly kill you.
You are the person closest to him.
You brought the shield.
Soldiers.
Arrest the princess.
You fools, what are you waiting for?
I will take my son from their hands.
But if it turns out that you are
responsible for these...
I did not do anything.
I am your friend who stands
tall in front of you.
I will accept your words now.
However, Olof...
He will be punished for
what he did to my Alps.
If Öktem is punished for
destroying the village...
I will pay for every drop of blood I shed.
Don't worry, Olof.
When the time comes, you will
pay that price...
Respected warrior of Rome.
We are very clear, Osman
Bey, as you have seen.
If you want, let's talk about what
we're going to do next.
We'll talk.
You can't go back, Osman.
Have mercy on me, my God...
and protect my father.
Break the door.
Search!
Look for her everywhere.
How long can you escape?
Princess.
Osman fell for the trick and we will
wait.
Tell me everything
before I kill you.
Talk!
You shouldn't do that, Olof.
I faithfully executed the plan.
Why didn't you allow me to
cut off Osman's head?
Tell me.
Frigg also agrees with me.
She kidnapped Alaaddin for us.
We can't destroy him like that, moreover,
this would be Dan's death decision.
Do you want to lose another brother?
I won't sacrifice another brother.
Then we'll play this game
by my rules.
Alaaddin is in our hands and
Osman will find him.
But he won't get out of there alive.
I will not barter.
I will attack Yenişehir.
and kill his son.
Why are things so difficult, Olof?
Osman will die anyway
while saving Alaaddin.
And you will enter the city
quietly and take your brother.
Then I will bring the Nicaea army and
destroy the city of Yenişehir.
And then...
You will return to Constantinople
as a hero.
Not me...
but us.
And after I sit on the throne, we will
be hell for all the Turks.
I support you because you
are valuable to me, Olof.
I want to trust you, Kantakuzenos.
Be careful not to disappoint me.
If you make a mistake, I will
cut off your head.
Wheel tracks point to this point.
Osman.
Bala, what's happening?
What happened?
They kidnapped Alaaddin.
But we found the tracks
of the wheels, my Bey.
My Bey, the traces brought us here but...
the road splits in two ways.
I will kill
whoever did this to my son.
So, Kantakuzenos was right.
We will follow the tracks of the carriage.
Half of the Alps will go from this side.
Aktemur, you will go to the tribe of
Öktem Bey with Turgut Bey.
You will bring the bodies of the martyrs.
You will search the tribe.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
And we'll go find our son, come on.
Damn you, you little mouse!
Kill me! Come on, what
are you waiting for?
You will live for a while until we kill
your father.
Then you will all die.
I won't remain a prisoner in the
hands of the enemy...
and my father won't fall into your trap.
Kill me!
Today we will take our revenge on Osman.
For Valhalla!
- For Valhalla!
I really like the fresh
fish you make, Leo.
Let me taste it.
Get ready, Leo!
While Osman goes behind Alaaddin...
we're going to rescue Dan from
the dungeon.
The situation is complex
and Alps are everywhere.
They close all the shops.
I smell your fear, Leo, or are
you really afraid?
No, I'm not afraid.
When are we going to the dungeon?
Don't be in a hurry, Leo.
A big guest will come to Yenişehir, we
have to meet him first.
Cerkutay.
Alps!
In the name of Allah.
Don't come.
The box is empty, my Bey.
He wrote in his own blood, my Bey.
He says "don't come."
If they hurt my son, I won't let them rest in
this world and the hereafter, Osman.
Don't worry, Bala.
However, we should be careful.
Our son has seen their trap.
Now, listen to me well.
I will try to be patient and tolerant...
but what about the people?
You should at least bring them the
corpses of their sons, Öktem Bey.
What should I do, Hatun?
The Sheikh restricted my movement.
How can I get over his words?
It is not permissible to ignore the
Sheikh's words.
But if you object, they will think
that there is sedition.
You didn't say that when you were
next to the Sheikh, Bayındır.
I am willing to sacrifice
myself for you, Öktem Bey.
However, you almost fought
the men of Osman Bey.
The blood was going to be shed, so
I decided to act like this.
It isn't appropriate for us to leave the bodies
of our martyrs in the hands of the infidels.
This is it.
Bayındır.
Don't cover up, Bengi Hatun.
They are not well.
Don't do that, Hatun.
Don't.
You should've held the hands of the infidels
who killed these valiants, not mine.
Now, let me.
I will see them.
Don't do that, Hatun.
Don't.
Go away, Öktem Bey.
I will see them.
Batur.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Sarkis.
God has sent you.
From this direction.
Messengers have come from
Constantinople, Ayşe Hatun.
They want to see Osman Bey.
Osman Bey isn't here.
I'll let you meet Malhun Hatun.
Please.
Emperor Andronikos asked us to
deliver this to Osman Bey.
He sent his regards to him.
When Osman Bey comes, I
will give him.
Now, you can go.
Let it be good, Inshallah.
When Osman Bey finds my dear Alaaddin
and bring him safely...
we will know what the Emperor wants.
Son.
Oh my Allah.
Aladdin!
We got you.
Aladdin, dear Aladdin.
- Aladdin!
- Is he okay?
- Father.
- Thank Allah.
It's fine, it's fine.
Come on, son.
Come on.
Aladdin, my son.
Right now!
Alps!
You tried to take my son away from me.
No power can take you out of my hands.
Yes.
Attack! Kill them all!
Son.
I took care of you like you
were my son.
But I couldn't keep the promise
I made to my mom.
Dear Batur.
While I was saying I'm going to
have your wedding...
and see you as a Bey...
Now I will wrap you in a white shroud.
Hatun.
Don't cry.
Batur became a martyr.
We don't deserve to cry.
No crying anymore.
No crying.
It's revenge time.
It's revenge time but...
do you have the courage to hold Osman
accountable for this?
Öktem Bey.
If it wasn't for Osman...
my brother..
would be here and alive now.
Osman is the one who
caused my brother's death.
What is Osman's fault?
If you are looking for the guilty
then I am here woman.
I'm the one who sent him
to the border.
I'm the one who sent him, Hatun.
Open your eyes, Öktem Bey!
Open!
You still trust Osman.
See the truth, please.
Osman is the only culprit.
This happened to us because he
makes agreements with the infidels.
You weren't allowed to take Alps
but Turgut went and took them.
He will stop our revenge.
And our blood will be left on the ground.
Not just this.
They will want to kill you, Öktem Bey!
They want your
soul and your position.
Hatun...
I don't fear death.
My place is known...
and my tribe is well known.
Let him come and kill me if he dares.
Don't say that, Öktem Bey.
This is not a brave war, don't you see?
They will betray you.
They will make agreements with the
infidels and trick us.
They brought our martyrs.
Why does Turgut Bey stay here?
Why doesn't he go?
Will they put a guard on us, Öktem Bey?
Don't give in to your
anger, don't do this.
I tell you we have martyrs.
This isn't the right time
to talk about this, Hatun.
- From now on...
- There will be no more than this!
I'll bury my brother...
but I will not bury you.
Öktem Bey, I will not put
you under the soil.
Despite you, I won't.
If I must disobey your order to protect you, I will, Öktem Bey!
You should know that.
Don't say that, Hatun.
Mother. Father.
Don't do this.
Let's do our last duty for
my uncle.
You're right my daughter, let's do it.
Alps!
Come on.
Take out my son.
They won't stop.
They will cause us many misfortunes.
Yenişehir
Your girls have done well, my love.
Do you think they have another option?
This is our play area.
Leo works as much as girls.
He brought the prison
(dungeon) map.
They're keeping Dan here.
There are many men here.
Cowards.
Then, we will burn the whole city.
Or we'll make some of them sleep.
Understood.
That's why you switched torches in prison.
You are...
my biggest strength, Frigg.
Together...
We are strong together.
What is happening to us?
Alps!
There is an intrusion.
Olof.
So, you came.
Come on, Bala.
Alaaddin.
it's our turn.
They will stop where we want, my Bey.
Alps!
Back off!
Archers.
Armor wall!
O, Allah!
I admire your intelligence so much, my love.
I know.
My love.
Do you smell death?
Dan.
Brother.
Dan, my brother.
Osman, I'll make you pay for this!
I will flay your skin while
you are alive, Osman!
Dan!
Olof.
I knew you would come.
It doesn't matter.
Osman will pay for this.
Come on.
Faster.
The guards are waking up.
Be careful, Alps!
Kill them!
There is an infiltration, Alps!
Close the doors, Alps!
Don't let them escape.
- It's explosives.
- Careful, Ayşe.
Ayşe!
They are running away, Ayşe.
- Come on, come on!
- Ignobles!
Oh God, what's going on?
Protect us all, Jesus Christ.
Oh, baby.
Don't be afraid, I'm on your side.
Do not stay in the alleys, enter the
houses, there is infiltration.
This way, Alps!
Alps! Catch them.
Go after them!
Run, run!
Run!
Hold on, Alaaddin.
My son, hold on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Sit down.
Sit here.
Sit down, son.
You came out alive
out of forty people.
Is there anyone braver than you?
Thank Allah.
You're fine son, you're fine.
- Father.
- Yes.
It was because of me.
No, no.
Alps!
Give him water.
Open your mouth.
Drink, drink.
You are fine.
You saved us from the trap
with what you wrote.
They are coming, my Bey.
Come on, come on.
Come on, son.
Hold on.
I will, father.
Come on, Bala.
Come on, Alps!
Everyone knows their job.
Ayşe.
We couldn't catch up, Malhun.
The prisoners and the man
with them escaped.
And I sent our Alps after them.
We will catch
them, Inshallah.
They escaped.
But there are still two
people inside, Ayşe.
Alps!
We are looking for two
people, a man and a woman.
The woman was hiding her
face, it's hard to find her but...
the man is injured.
Do what you have to do
and find them, Ayşe.
We will find them.
Come on, Alps! Come on.
Fool.
You're injured.
How do you come here when
you are in this situation? Say it.
Did you leave a trace behind?
No.
You idiot.
I won't let you spoil my game.
You can't kill me, Frigg.
I can.
Hello?
Martha, Mr. Leo.
Martha.
Malhun Hatun.
Welcome.
Please, don't bother me.
It's inattention.
What happened to
your hand, Martha?
The screw in the fabric box.
When I saw the silk, I didn't
notice the nail.
What is that sound?
They must be the little guests.
Mice.
It must be mice.
How does a small mouse
make this sound?
Not one, but there are three.
However, one of them is dead.
But the two are still alive.
It's there.
Malhun, the Alps in prison woke up.
Tell Mr. Leo...
to get rid of all mice.
And you be careful.
Show your hand to the doctor.
You would ruin everything.
You clumsy freak.
"Show your hand to the doctor."
Batur.
My mother's memory.
My brother.
You were martyred but...
your sister is in pain.
My valiant.
Öktem Bey.
I know...
we just buried your brother...
and your pain is recent...
But for the sake of those who
remained in the tribe...
I have a job that can't wait.
On such a sad day...
What is the task that
can not wait, Turgut Bey?
I will search your tribe.
What is left in our tribe but
bereaved mothers?
What are you going to look for?
Taxes from Constantinople
to Macri are missing.
Kantakuzenos thinks you have gold.
My job is to find them.
Will you look for the gold of Rome in a
Turkish tribe with a word from the infidel?
Turgut Bey?
Turgut Bey.
You say Batur Alp stole
Macri's taxes, right?
Nothing like this could ever
happen, it's impossible.
I buried my brother's body in the grave.
What are you saying, Turgut Bey?
I say...
Let's prevent the slander that
they accuse our martyrs with.
Let us do our job.
Let's get rid of that accusation.
Stop, Hatun.
Stop.
You are searching for the truth.
We know the truth.
Do your job.
A slander only embarrasses its owner.
Well.
Aktemur.
Alps.
How much do the infidels pay
for each person, Hüseyin?
I don't know, my Bey. They must have
taken 10 bags of gold.
What ruthless infidels they are.
Osman does not take a quarter of this.
So, the tax of the village...
is more than a chest of gold.
A big chest of gold.
Shiny.
I say gold, Hüseyin.
Look.
Yes, my Bey.
If Öktem really did this...
the gold must be in this tribe.
And if they tricked Öktem...
the gold must be in this tribe anyway.
It is true what you are saying, my Bey.
How dare you confirm my words?
Spread your Alps everywhere.
Find the gold for me, Hüseyin.
So that I can make you a Bey.
What happened, Hüseyin? You
froze when you heard about gold.
We will send a messenger to Sencer Bey.
You mean Sencer, the brother-in-law of
the Sultan, right?
Yeah, who did you think?
Come on, write what I say.
The Honorable Sencer Bey.
As you know, Osman is a reckless person.
He burned the lands and turned them
into ashes.
He totally destroyed it.
Othman is dragged into a war.
This war will make us control the trade.
Hold on, son.
Hold on.
You are the hero today.
My son.
Son.
My father.
Come on.
come up.
Hold on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, Alps.
Stop.
Hold on, my son.
Hold on.
You can't escape from your end, Osman.
You also won't run away.
Alps!
Boran.
Ayaz!
Shields!
O Allah!
Dumrul.
The fire will be the end of you.
People who are so skilled to
kidnap my son from Yenişehir...
won't leave traces like this behind.
The enemy is a new.
But they are all the same.
What shall we do then, my Bey?
As long as they set a trap
for us by leaving traces...
we will set a trap for them.
We will act exactly like them.
We will retreat.
The war will happen where we want it.
Not only this.
They'll erect a wall of shields and try
to withdraw when they fall into the trap.
We won't be able to catch any of them.
That is why we will press
them with arrows and attack them.
Until we drag them to where we want.
When they get there...
The only thing they will
give is their life.
Cerkutay.
Tell Boran.
Your order, my Bey.
You will stop where we want.
Allah is the greatest!
O Allah!
Ignite!
The truth is Allah!
We will not allow them, brothers.
Fires don't catch easily.
However, Cerkutay's lungs are strong.
To the right, to the right!
To the right.
Remember Cerkutay!
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay never dies!
Come on.
The field became ours.
Shoot the arrows of the Turks.
Allah is eternal!
Allah is the greatest!
You put your hand on my son.
I will cut off your heads one by one.
But now it's your turn.
You can't enter.
I don't allow it.
Your words are valid in
Yenişehir, commander.
Stick to your limits.
The extent of my limits is beyond
your imagination, Hatun.
Go away and let me do my job.
My sword is sharper than
your dagger, you should know that.
There is no turning back
on this, commander.
Hatun.
I told you to go away.
This time
I won't be forgiving.
There is no other way to reveal the truth.
Can't you hear my words, Hatun?
Alçiçek.
Move, my daughter.
Let them search.
I have nothing to hide from anyone.
I'm curious if they'll be able to
look at our faces after this.
Go in and search.
Father.
Enter.
Alps.
Kutlu Alp.
What's up, Kutlu Alp?
We're looking but it looks like
there's nothing, my Bey.
There is basically nothing.
You are looking for
something that does not exist.
Are you searching people's tents after
failing to find anything?
Alcicek.
Are you searching people's tents after
failing to find anything?
Alcicek.
Hatun.
I believe your words.
And I know you don't have gold.
Why are you searching then?
Because it is a matter of state.
It's my job.
And I do what I have to do.
If you trust my words...
...just wait.
The more we remain silent and wait
the more you accuse us, Subasi!
Uncle, father and now this gold!
It's one trouble after anoter, I know.
I know that
I know it's a tough situation.
But I also know that
the brave Hatun who beat me in the duel...
...must know how to deal with this.
Don't remind me that, Subasi!
It didn't end well for me.
They say "every cloud has a silver lining"
I know you.
I saw you.
I know you wouldn't do that.
I and Osman Bey are on your side
Alps!
Gather up!
My Bey, check it out!
Alps!
Come on
You are wasting your time.
Hurry up Alps!
Come on, take it out!
Get it out quickly!
What is this?
Is this Roman gold?
Turgut Bey!
This is not ours
Look at that!
Oktem Bey.
We trust you and stand behind you.
And is this what you do in return?
In this case..
It's over, Oktem Bey.
You have been proven guilty, Oktem Bey.
I don't know about this.
It must be them...
They slandered us.
They set their game
a long time ago, Turgut Bey.
What happens next will be decided
by the court.
Good.
Have you hidden the gold well?
I hid it when I was
on my night shift, madam.
I would take a bit of you with me...
...if Leo wasn't going to give me much more.
Attaboy.
So you have been working with Leo
for long years.
So you did bring the dungeon's map, huh?
Yes ma'am
Where is Mr. Leo?
I haven't seen him.
I'll give you your reward in return of
your service for Leo.
Do you hear the sound of death?
You do not.
Yenisehir.
Did I hear right, mother?
Did they kidnap my brother?
Your father went after them,
Aladdin will return safely, Inshallah.
Mother, Alps are waiting outside.
Order me to bring my brother back!
We don't need that, my brave son.
You will meet your brother soon.
Are you saying this to stop me, mother?
Why would I want to stop Bey Orhan?
So what about all the alps
who fill the tribe?
Malhun Hatun, Kantakuzenos has arrived.
Let him.
Malhun Hatun.
Orhan Bey.
I salute you both with respect.
Welcome.
Osman Bey will be here shortly.
You can wait in the entrance tent.
He won't make it anyway.
Of course.
What is the reason for your visit,
Kantakuzenos?
I hosted Osman Bey in my city.
I wanted to return the visit.
And of course,
there is that court issue.
I hope you have nothing to do with the
abduction of my brother.
Don't worry little Bey.
I hope your father will come back
with your brother safely.
Osman Bey is coming.
Brother.
Son, son!
- Welcome, Osman Bey.
- Welcome to you.
You are the guest.
I am so glad you found your son
and came back safe and sound
All this happened after
you and Olof came.
They tried to kill our children.
They set a trap on us.
This didn't start because I or Olof came.
It all started after you saved the emperor.
Alright then, I'll finish it.
That's exactly why I'm here.
I want Frigg and Ophelia to
get the ending they deserve.
Ophelia is there
And the throne is there.
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be next to the emperor?
I am a servant of Rome.
Oktem Bey's trial is justice for Rome.
This is as important as the throne.
We do not need the justice of Rome
while we have our justice.
What's gonna happen,
is gonna happen.
My Bey, its from Turgut Bey.
Gold was found in Oktem Bey's tribe.
What you said happened, Kantakuzenos.
So you'll hand me Oktam Bey,
won't you?
He committed the crime against you.
But he is from us.
Let's meet in the tribe
of Oktem Bey tomorrow.
I will punish him myself.
I don't care about the rest if
you punish him in front of me
- Then see you tomorrow.
- Go well.
- Boran
- My Bey!
Invite everyone to the court.
As you order, my Bey.
I will take revenge on Osman, Olof.
Don't worry brother.
Our friend already avenged us.
Osman and his son died.
Vengeance!
It will not end with Osman's death!
Every Turk I will kill from now on
will go into the grave without a finger!
Do you...
Do you think that they will have graves?
They will be food for crows!
We lost
What did we lose?
The trap...
They set a trap for us, Olof!
Is Osman alive?
You were going to avenge Saga!
You were going to avenge our men!
And I lost my brother Lef, Olof!
Now our vengance is greater!
I will avenge with my own hands, Olof!
Give me one more chance.
We will take revenge with
Kantakuzenos' army.
How will this happen?
Kantakuzenos poisoned the emperor.
Ophelia will be held responsible.
And since Ophelia will die as a traitor...
...the throne will be Kantakuzenos'.
And the army of vengeance will be ours.
You are safe here.
Have you seen my father, Sarkis?
What do the soldiers want from you,
princess?
Why are you running away?
They did something to my father, Sarkis.
Maybe they killed him.
Whoever did this is trying to
put the blame on me!
Whoever attacked the arena did this as well.
Someone who wants the throne.
You shouldn't stay in the palace,
it's not safe here.
How? What should I do?
My father?
What about my father?
I have to get to my father!
They must have poisoned him!
Oh princess.
If they poisoned your father,
you won't be able to help him
What should I do?
You should hide somewhere
they can't find you.
And I will ask for help.
From whom?
From someone who helped us before.
What we are experiencing now
is because of the tasks of Osman Bey.
Osman Bey wants the interest of Beys
and all this is for the sake of conquests.
Who could have known that
such a calamity would happen?
Osman Bey will rule with justice.
Trust him.
Please be comfortable.
I do not trust anybody.
I don't make the same mistake
my father has done, Subasi.
Your anger is not good, Alcicek.
You know what it causes.
It happened unintentionally.
You have to get out quickly
Come on
Before the alps come!
You can't think about me right now!
You should see a healer!
It's not important.
Come on, get out.
I keep the dagger.
What you are doing is unpredictable.
You might get angry now
and stab him in my heart
You have a wound, man!
Why are you laughing for?
Come on, Alcicek, get out!
Come on.
We have a lot to do with you,
Alcicek Hatun.
Are you still talking about
such a small wound?!
How coward you are, Subasi!
Leave me.
I told you to leave me, Subasi!
Subasi, leave my hand
You are right.
I'm a coward.
I am the one who scares seven countries.
Aktemur, son of Gunduz Bey.
Subasi Aktemur.
My limbs tremble when
I look into your eyes
I am so afraid, Alcicek.
But you are also afraid!
You can't even say my name!
They kidnapped my son in my town!
And they didn't stop there.
They also took him prisoner.
Tell me now.
Which one of you will pay for this?
Are you going to pay?
Huh?
- Or will you pay?
- My Bey...
- We were changing the tor...
- Shut up!
I don't want another excuse.
In this path we have been dreaming of...
...there shall be no mistake.
You will continue
You will keep searching.
As you order, my Bey!
Get out now.
There is a message from Konur.
I will go to Constantinople.
They want to poison the emperor
and accuse Ophelia.
Can we trust Ophelia, my Bey?
We'll know who we can trust
after we take Ophelia.
My Bey, I have prepared the alps.
I will only go with Kumral Abdal.
While I am taking Ophelia...
..he will cure the emperor
You can go out.
Yes my Bey.
My Bey.
Subasi Aktemur.
He was on a mission in Oktem Bey's tribe.
I am the only reason
why the prisoner escaped.
That escaper...
..he tried to kill our son.
He is free for now.
But do not worry.
His life won't last long.
Take extra precautions.
My brave son.
You did not surrender to the enemy.
You resisted to honor your father.
Praise be!
Sorry, mother.
I've caused you trouble.
I should have been careful.
Don't say that, son.
You cannot do anything
when the enemy attacks from behind...
Can I?
Come in Orhan, come in.
I will check your sister.
- Brother
You look healthy, brother.
I'm fine brother.
They attacked me before,
now they attack you.
We are at death's door,
we shall end the conflict.
There is no conflict between us, brother.
It's just...
Just what brother?
There cannot be any conflict
between brothers!
How is your hand?
It is getting better.
Take this dagger.
You deserve it, brother.
They attack you to kill you.
They attack me to capture me.
Even the enemy is not intrested in me.
So always keep this with yourself.
So that this won't happen again.
Come on, have a rest.
Malhun?
Can I come in?
Come, Bala, come.
Bengi Hatun.
She buried Batur today.
Every time I think about it,
my heart burns, Bala.
Allah shall never let anyone
go through that.
Children feel different, Malhun.
When their nail hurts...
...your heart shatters.
Time flies.
How small he was!
And now he's become a great Bey!
I sewed it for Orhan, right?
What if I had lost Orhan, Bala?
Whenever I remember, I feel like my mind
and heart are going out of their place!
What if I couldn't catch up?
What if I was the one who buried her son?
When I saw Aladdin's bloody hat...
I thought I wouldn't be able to live
with that pain, I would die.
I wanted to scream.
I wanted to make the world shake.
I couldn't scream.
I couldn't scream
All those Alps behind me...
I hid the pain of my heart
behind my weapon.
Then I tried to save my son.
The destiny of our children was already
written before they were born.
We have saved them from countless enemies.
And many more are to come.
Malhun Hatun...
Your children are my children.
Never forget this.
Not to speak of being jealous...
I am ready to burn the whole world
for our children.
We are not just wives of Osman Bey.
We are not just his warriors.
We are the mothers of
the almighty state!
Even if our hearts burn...
Our almighty state and our case
comes first.
And then our children...
Then our motherhood.
That's right.
We would sacrifice a thousand children
for this state.
Even if our hearts burn...
Our job as mothers of the state
comes before all else.
Thank Allah, our valiants stand together.
They stand tall like mountains.
We will stand together too.
Surely.
We will do this in order for
this almighty state to live forever
This is our duty.
This is our destiny.
Enough already!
At any cost...
...this time I will tell him
I would look after his children.
What if he condemns me?
Is there anything wrong with love?
No!
No, I will tell him.
Hey you! Cerkutay!
Love ya!
I will say it.
Smells nice.
This will ease my job.
Hungry I am!
I can't hear!
I can't hear.
Cerkutay!
Eat, Cerkutay, eat
Eat.
Eat but.. Listen to me too,
okay?
I know that a Hatun
usually doesn't say that.
But..
I'll say it!
Bon Apetit!
Let me fill it back!
I will bring more!
The comfort lies in silence.
Enjoy it.
What I mean is...
Cerkutay...
I.. I will tell you...
I am in love with you!
Cerkutay!
Let's get out!
Cerkutay!!!!
I'm telling you, we're going brother!
What are you saying
I don't hear I don't hear!
We'll go brother, come on!
Go on, brother. Godspeed!
Go well.
Come on brother, come on,
you're coming with me.
Come on.
Come on brother.
Boran!
Yes brother, yes.
Keep this.
Don't eat it. I'll eat it later.
Okay brother.
Boran Alp!
Is Cerkutay deaf?
Unfortunately, Ulgen sister.
His ears are no longer working.
But don't be sad, it's temporary.
Come on.
- So delicious!
- Come on, come on.
Have I been talking in vain?!?
How unlucky I am!
Aladdin.
My valiant son.
My miracle kid.
Aladdin.
I do not differentiate between my children.
A father's heart is so big...
...that there is a place for all of you.
You are like tree branches.
Together but in different.
Your characters...
... and your skills
are different from each other
Son.
Never forget this.
I've heard it all, father.
Why would I tell you if I thought
you wouldn't hear it, son?
I knew you weren't asleep.
Where are you going?
To the infidels.
To give you a safe homeland.
However...
...keeping this state safe...
...is your duty.
You shouldn't feel despair
and give up.
You will get up on your feet.
And you will be patient.
Patience brings salvation.
Patience brings...
...an eternal state.
And that country...
...in your hands...
...will rule the whole world.
Trust me, father.
The horses are ready, my Bey.
Eyvallah (Thanks).
Where are you going, Cerkutay?
YES MY BEY!
What is he saying?
My Bey, he still can't hear.
Obviously.
He still can't hear.
Go to Oktem Bey...
Go to Oktem Bey's tribe tomorrow.
Side with Turgut Bey.
As you order my Bey.
Agreed, my Bey!
Brother!
Cerkutay.
We are not going.
Stop, Cerkutay.
Oktam's Tribe
My Allah shall forbid
anyone going through this.
Slander hits hard.
They casted us down.
They took our liver.
This despair...
...doesn't fit in us, Oktem Bey.
No it's not.
Thank you.
The reason for everything that happened is
Osman Bey.
We are paying the price
for him to found a state.
But this is not going to end well.
I do not trust Osman at all.
He will unite with the infidels.
They will burn your father, Alcicek.
Just like how they burned Batur...
...they will burn your father too.
Mother...
...what if what we're doing is wrong?
...what if it is best to trust Osman Bey?
You know...
My father thought well of him all the time.
He helped us a lot
Now why would he hurt my father?
The same reason why he hurt Batur, Alcicek!
And now will he
stand against the emperor...
...and stand with your father, huh?
Is it only me...
....who has gone through all these?
What trust are you talking about, Alcicek?
Let me clear the table.
I know what to do.
Sent by Osman Bey, my Bey.
Osman Bey is not coming.
He says don't let Kantakuzenos
take Oktem Bey.
I hope there's nothing wrong.
Constantinople
We will attack the enemy from here.
Are you afraid, Kumral Abdal?
You don't take the
cowards with you, Osman Bey!
That's right.
Also, with Sari Saltug, we have...
...experienced a lot
in the lands of infidels!
But Osman Bey...
We toured all their lands
and never saw anything like this.
Nice.
The city is nice too.
But its rulers aren't.
We will give them a lesson.
- Is it only two of us?
- Let's go.
Come on.
The end of the world is coming, my Sheik.
Humanity is deceived by Satan all the time.
A brother envies another.
You are talking about the envy that
throw Yusuf in the well, right?
The envy that befell that beautiful prophet...
...will do anything to us, my Sheik.
Yusuf's brothers were deceived by satan.
They were so deceived.
Our master Yakup's love for Yusuf,
peace be upon him, was so great.
His brothers were angry and jealous of him.
They were jealous so much that
they thought of killing their brother.
They tried to kill him.
They took the beautiful-faced Prophet
with them and threw him into a well.
Then they stained his shirt with blood
and give it to his father, our master Yakup
They said that "Yusuf was eaten by a wolf...
...Yusuf is no longer with us, he died."
As soon as our master Yakup grabbed
Yusuf's shirt in his hand
He figured it out at that exact moment.
That Yusuf's brothers were lying.
And after that day, Prophet Yakup went blind
because of crying too much.
He said "the eyes that do not see Yusuf...
...shall not see the world either."
Joseph's brothers were jealous of their
father's love for Yusuf...
And they threw him in the well, right?
But they caused the greatest pain
of their father.
Their envy was so enormous that...
...they couldn't even tell the truth.
As for Yusuf, he came out of that well.
He became a slave.
He was slandered and imprisoned.
But he was always alive in Yakup's heart.
Yusuf got out of prison,
became Egypt's governor.
Someday, Yusuf's brothers went to him.
Yusuf recognized them.
And he confronted them.
But he did not despise them at all.
His brothers caused that beautiful face
prophet a heavy trouble...
...because of their envy against him.
As for him, he said to them
"You are not the one who brought me here"
"It is my Lord who brought me here"
His brothers asked for forgiveness from him.
They swore that Allah has placed you
in a higher rank than us.
We were certainly wrong, they said.
And they believed in the
prophethood of Yusuf, peace be upon him.
Hadrat Yusuf showed mercy to his brothers.
He went the way of The Most Merciful.
He forgave them.
He considered that everything
that happened to him was from Allah.
He didn't see any evil.
He was patient.
He was patient in the most beautiful way.
My dears, everything that Allah
has blessed us with is good.
We are sometimes sad about some incidents.
But in the end, the goodness inside
becomes clear to us.
The thing that keep prophet Yusuf alive
is his faith.
Life will pass through exams and hardships.
You should know this.
In every incident, you will go the way
the messengers of Allah went.
And you will find your light.
Prophet Yusuf is the one who forgave his
brothers who threw him into a well.
We shall not break anyone's heart.
Become a forgiver.
Let the verses of Allah and
the stories of his messengers...
And the honorable hadiths of our Messenger
guide you.
- Amen
So, dears.
This was your class today.
My Bey, my Bey!
There is a sound!
My Bey!
No.
Did you think we were alone,
Kumral Abdal?
Check them!
In which city was the Turk left alone?!
The intelligence formations
that we established have begun to operate.
Praise be for the valiants and sisters!
My Bey, Olof's men are going to the arena,
they're getting ready.
I'm going to the arena.
You go to the palace.
Death and life comes from Allah.
But do your best to keep emperor alive so
no one we don't like sits on the throne.
I will do my best, if Allah permits, my Bey!
Let's go.
We are ready Olof.
We'll go to the arena.
Ophelia and dog Sarkis are there.
This will end today.
Come on.
Odin's ravens are going to kill!
We are coming!
I am a healer.
I came to heal him.
We can't get you inside.
I have to!
For the sake of the Emperor's health.
Check the door.
What is that noise about?
What's happening?
Who are you?
Soldiers, soldiers!
Sleep a while.
Emperor, Osman Bey sent me.
I came to heal you.
Osman Bey.
What is happening here?
Who are you?
Stop.
Let him.
Let's find out what kind of poison it is.
If there is life, there is hope.
What are those infidels doing here?
Leave!
Only thing we lacked was the infidels(!)
We'll solve this with peace, Oktem Bey.
They came again, what are they asking for?
Leave here!
Come on
Kantakuzenos.
Turgut Bey.
This incident will be solved today.
Gold came out of this tribe
as I heard
Given that the evidence is obvious...
Infidel!
You killed my alps!
You put gold in my tribe!
How dare you show up?
Come on, Kantakuzenos.
Let's go into the tent.
Will you invite this infidel to our tent
and host him too, Turgut Bey?
The blood of my uncle and our alps
is still on the ground!
I did not come to the tribe of someone
who killed my fellows...
...and stole my taxes.
Where is Osman Bey?
Neither me nor my alps!
We didn't do any of what you said.
Do not confuse us with you, you infidel!
Osman Bey will come.
Everyone will be waiting quietly until then.
The place where he will wait is not my tent.
If that's the case, we'll wait here.
Constantinople
I want dog Sarkis and Ophelia alive.
Run!
Sir Sarkis.
The emperor's men came to take princess.
They found us.
Don't worry princess.
We'll get you out of here.
Follow me.
It is clear that Osman Bey will not come.
Turgut Bey.
I ask you to hand me Oktem Bey
so that justice may be served.
Don't you hear?
We will wait for Osman Bey.
Nothing will be done before Osman Bey
comes, Kantakuzenos.
But Osman Bey promised me his life.
You will hand him over to me.
And I'll kill him in this tribe.
Hey freedom fighters!
You've come to the end of the road,
Princess Ophelia.
Slaves!
Give her to me.
I will never betray the emperor.
To whom do you raise your swords?
When my father heals...
You will all pay for this!
Princess Ophelia.
I came here to arrest you.
Who are you?
I am Olof.
Loyal leader of the emperor.
The rebellion started here,
with this traitor by your side.
And it will end where it began.
It's not over until I say it's over, Olof.
I don't know whom you serve to.
You won't take the princess
before you kill me.
Glad to hear that.
You will pay for all of this.
And it's today.
Whenever I point my axe at someone,
I find you in front of me, Osman!
Always point your axe
in the right direction.
You protected the guilty Oktem first,
and now you protect the traitor princess.
The walker of the right path
does not step back from any difficulty.
You killed my alps because of a slander!
You hid gold in my tribe.
You smeared my Beyship!
You came here and stopped me!
Alps.
And now you want my life in my tribe
in front of my people!
From now on,
my sword will secure the justice.
Alps! Alps!
Stop!
Why don't you hear listen to me?!
Alps!
Ophelia
They will take you, princess.
Catch her, don't let her escape!
She will go out, but you will stay.
If you stay, I will stay to kill you.
Come on then.
Come on.
It will end where it began.
Anyone who tries to stop us
is condemned to death.
My fire will burn you Osman.
I don't know to whom you serve.
But as long as I face you...
...I will end you one by one.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com